

Kelvin Mijaya

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING MANAGER

Contact

- Springhill Terrace Residence, South Jakarta, Indonesia
- kelvinmijaya@gmail.com
- (+62) 812 8833 3592
- in @kelvinmijaya
- www.kelvinmijaya.com

Skills

Technical

Javascript, React, NextJS, Golang, PHP, Codeigniter, Laravel

Communication

English (Advanced level 12 Wall Street English), Indonesia (Native)

Leadership & Management

7 Habis for managers (Franklin Covey), Mentor at Devcamp Tokopedia Academy, Mentor at Next Coach

About

I've been in the software engineering industry for 10 years and I'm enjoying it. Whether I'm focusing on websites, mobile apps, or UX, it is always a life-changing experience. Lastly, I want to contribute my knowledge and experience.

Work Experience

Tokopedia

Jan 2017 - Dec 2023

Software Engineering Manager

- Plan and execute long-term strategies that benefit the team and the company
- Monitor and optimize performance related to speed, responsiveness, and core web vitals
- Collaborate with product managers, designers, and other stakeholders to translate their requirements into technical specifications.
- Foster a culture of continuous learning within the frontend team, encouraging skill development and knowledge sharing.

OVO Finansial (Taralite)

Nov 2015 - Jan 2017

UI/UX & Frontend Lead

- Develop a website using ReactJS & Redux
- Working closely with the Backend team
- Developing UX for User and business needs
- · Create user testing and user Interface

Bounche

Oct 2014 - Sep 2015

Frontend Web Developer

- Develop a website using PHP, Codeigniter, and Laravel
- Contribute to the User Experience process
- Create a custom JS Script to speed up the development process

Education History

Bachelor of Computer Science

BINUS University

• School of Information System